

MONTANARO **SANTIAGO**Web developer

- Villa Gobernador Gálvez, Santa Fe, Argentina
- ☑ santmon99@gmail.com
- +54 9 341-280-4346

SOCIAL

- in @santiago montanaro
- **y** @santimontana_
- @ @IIIIiiiiiiiiji
- @santiagomontanaro
- Portfolio

PROFILE

I'm a Systems Analyst student with no experience and wanting to enter the world of work. But what I'm really passionate about is web development. I am not an expert but I know how to function effectively, it is something that I like to do and therefore motivates me to continue learning. I consider myself a responsible, proactive and committed person, but above all wanting to work, gain experience and grow both professionally and personally.

SKILLS

- HTML
- PHP
- Css
- MySQL
- Python
- Git
- Javascript

WORK EXPERIENCE

ENGLISH TRANSLATOR

From 2021 - Current | Freelancer

I'm in charge of doing translations from Spanish to English on the Freelancer platform.

ARCHITECTURAL DESIGN AND RENDERS

From 2020 - Current | Black & White (House and Furniture Design Company)

I am in charge of the realization of photorealistic 3D renderings of interiors and exteriors based on architectural plans of houses, buildings or furniture. Software that I currently use:

- SketchUp
- V-Ray

TECHNICAL SERVICE

From 2015 to 2019 | Independently

Repair of PC's, mobile devices and / or networks, in addition to:

- Maintenance
- Software / Hardware
- Installation

EDUCATION

SYSTEMS ANALYST

I.S.E.I. 4030 - Higher Institute in Computer Studies

2019 - In progress

Tertiary education

ELECTRONIC TECHNICIAN

E.E.T. Nº 1175 Dr. Gabriel Carrasco

2017 - 2018

Secondary education

ELECTRONIC TECHNICIAN

E.E.T.P.I. Nº 8235 Engineer Enrique B. Gomara

2012 - 2014

Secondary education

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- English

INTERESTS









Music

Gaming

Travel

Read